<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on FOOD VIBES</title>
    <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on FOOD VIBES</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://foodvib.es/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avocado Pie Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/avocado_pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/avocado_pie/</guid>
      <description>Add the avocados and cream cheese to a mixing bowl and mix well. Add the condensed milk, lemon and lime juices and a pinch of salt. Beat until fluffy. Pour the filling into the pie crust and refrigerate for four hours.
Serve chilled with a dollop of whipped cream.   2 avocados 2 limes, juiced 1 lemon, juiced ½ cup cream cheese 1 cup sweetened, condensed milk salt whipped cream 9″ graham cracker pie crust Makes one pie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Açaí Bowl Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/acai_bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/acai_bowl/</guid>
      <description>Cut all fruit into bite sized pieces and set aside. Blend frozen açaí berries with hemp milk and pour into a bowl. Layer granola on top of açaí mixture. Layer fruit on top of granola. Drizzle with honey and sprinkle with pollen.
Serve immediately.   ¾ cup frozen açaí berries ¼ cup hemp milk 1 cup granola ½ banana ½ kiwi ½ cup strawberries ½ cup blueberries ½ cup pineapple honey bee pollen Makes one bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bacon Sandwich Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/bacon_sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/bacon_sandwich/</guid>
      <description>Cook bacon to preference in a preheated skillet over medium heat and set aside on a paper towel to absorb some of the grease. Cook eggs to preference in the same skillet using the existing bacon grease. At the same time, toast the bread and spread the dressing on each side. Layer bacon, eggs, cheese and arugula inside bread.
Serve immediately.   3 bacon slices 2 eggs 2 bread slices ranch dressing 1 cheese slice arugula Makes one sandwich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Churros Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/baked_churros/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/baked_churros/</guid>
      <description>Mix cinnamon and sugar in a rectangular baking pan or container and set aside. Combine ½ cup of butter, salt and water in a sauce pan and bring to a boil. Pour mixture into a mixing bowl and add flour. Mix until incorporated, then slowly mix in eggs individually and finally mix in the vanilla. Spoon batter into a pastry bag with ½″ star tip and pipe into 6″ logs with 1″ spacing between rows onto a buttered baking sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bandito Rice Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/bandito_rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/bandito_rice/</guid>
      <description>Cook rice in oil in a large, preheated skillet over medium heat for about three minutes or until golden brown. Pour in chicken broth and bring to a boil. Mix in bouillon, cumin, cilantro, garlic and salt and pepper to taste. Add onion, bell pepper, tomato, corn and jalapeño. Return to a boil then cover and reduce heat to low. Cook for 20 minutes.
Serve warm.   1 cups white rice 1 tablespoons coconut oil 1½ cups chicken broth 1 cube chicken bouillon ½ teaspoon cumin, ground ½ cup cilantro, chopped 1 garlic clove, chopped salt black pepper ½ white onion, chopped ½ green bell pepper, chopped 1 tomato, seeded and chopped ½ cup of corn 1 jalapeño, chopped Makes six servings of rice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bloody Maria Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/bloody_maria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/bloody_maria/</guid>
      <description>Combine tequila with tomato juice, lime juice, two dashes each of hot sauce and worcestershire and two pinches of pepper and celery salt. Mix well and pour over ice.
Serve in a celery-salt-rimmed highball, garnished with a celery stalk and lime wedge.   2 ounces tequila blanco 4 ounces tomato juice 1 lime, juiced hot sauce worcestershire black pepper celery salt Makes one drink.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast Tacos Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/breakfast_tacos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/breakfast_tacos/</guid>
      <description>Cook bacon to preference in a preheated skillet over medium heat and set aside on a paper towel to absorb some of the grease. Cook eggs to preference in the same skillet using the existing bacon grease. Wrap eggs, bacon and arugula in warm tortillas. Sprinkle with cheese.
Serve with salsa.   2 bacon slices 2 eggs arugula 2 corn tortillas jack cheese, shredded Makes two tacos.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California Chicken Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/california_chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/california_chicken/</guid>
      <description>Mix everything except the chicken in a small bowl. Add salt and pepper to taste. Transfer to a sealable container, add the chicken and refrigerate for 30 minutes to 4 hours, turning at least once.
Discard marinade and grill chicken uncovered, turning once, for 12 minutes or until internal temperatures reach at least 170°F. Remove from the grill and slice into bite-sized strips.
Serve warm with tortillas and grilled vegetables.   2 chicken breasts, halved ½ cup coconut oil 4 limes, juiced ¼ cup cilantro, chopped 2 green onions, diced 1 garlic clove, diced 1 tablespoon honey 1 teaspoon cumin salt black pepper Makes four servings of grilled chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checksmix Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/checksmix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/checksmix/</guid>
      <description>Mix butter, worcestershire, hot sauce, salt, garlic and onion powders in a small bowl. Pour over mixture of cereal and crackers in an extra large mixing bowl. Sprinkle with furikake and mix well. Spread mixture in a thin layer on a large baking sheet and bake at 250°F for an hour, turning every 15 minutes.
Serve immediately or let cool and store.   ½ cup butter, melted 4 tablespoons worcestershire 4 teaspoons hot sauce 2 teaspoons salt 1½ teaspoon garlic powder ½ teaspoon onion powder 8 cups of mixed grain cereal 2 cups cheese crackers furikake Makes 10 cups of snack mix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chia Pudding Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/chia_pudding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/chia_pudding/</guid>
      <description>Dissolve honey in water. Mix in coconut milk and chia seeds. Cover and refrigerate overnight.
Serve with granola and fresh fruit or jam.   2 tablespoons honey 1 cup water 1 cup coconut milk ¼ cup chia seeds Makes one pudding cup.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coconut Cream Pie Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/coconut_cream_pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/coconut_cream_pie/</guid>
      <description>Bake about ¼ cup of the coconut on a baking sheet at 350°F for five minutes or until golden brown. Set aside. Combine the half and half, eggs, sugar, flour and salt in a saucepan and bring to a boil over low heat, stirring constantly. Remove from heat and add the ¾ cup un-toasted coconut and vanilla. Pour into pie crust and refrigerate for four hours or until cool.
Top with a layer of whipped cream and sprinkle evenly with toasted coconut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coconut Macaroons Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/coconut_macaroons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/coconut_macaroons/</guid>
      <description>Beat egg whites with sugar and vanilla in a mixing bowl until thick and foamy and set aside. In another large bowl, combine the coconut with the condensed milk. Fold in the egg whites mixture previously set aside. Using a tablespoon, drop batter by the spoonful onto a parchment lined cookie sheet and bake in a pre-heated oven at 250°F for 30 minutes or until golden.
Let the macaroons cool completely and remove from the parchment paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coconut Velvet Cake Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/coconut_velvet_cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/coconut_velvet_cake/</guid>
      <description>Whisk the flour, baking soda, cocoa powder, and salt together in a large bowl. Set aside. In a mixing bowl, beat the butter and vanilla until smooth. Slowly add the sugar, oil and egg yolks, beating until combined. Slowly add the dry ingredients in three additions, adding the first and second half of the buttermilk in between each, mixing just until incorporated. Separately, whisk the egg whites and vinegar until thick and foamy and then manually fold into the batter with a spatula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dharmic Salad Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/dharmic_salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/dharmic_salad/</guid>
      <description>Add mixed greens to a large bowl. Mix in sprouts, beets, carrots, cucumber and tomatoes. Add croutons, sprinkle with sunflower kernels and cheese. Drizzle ranch all over and sprinkle with salt and pepper.
Serve immediately.   3 ounces mixed salad greens ¼ cup broccoli sprouts ½ roasted red beet, shredded ½ large carrot, shredded ½ cucumber, sliced ½ heirloom tomato, diced croutons roasted sunflower kernels parmesan cheese ranch dressing salt black pepper Makes one salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Blondies Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/dirty_blondies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/dirty_blondies/</guid>
      <description>In a mixing bowl, combine the butter and sugar. Mix well. Add the vanilla, egg and salt and mix until smooth. Add the flour and mix until incorporated. Pour batter into a buttered 10″ baking pan and bake at 350°F for 25 minutes or until a toothpick inserted into the middle comes out clean. Cut into squares.
Serve warm with a scoop of your favorite ice cream.   ½ cup unsalted butter, melted 1 cup brown sugar 1½ teaspoons vanilla extract 1 egg salt 1 cup flour Makes 12 blondies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fries Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/fries/</guid>
      <description>Bring a couple inches of oil to 300°F in a large pot. Add the potatoes to the oil in batches, ensuring potatoes are fully submerged, cooking for 5 minutes or until golden brown. Remove each batch from the oil, place on a newspaper-lined baking sheet and sprinkle with salt and pepper.
Serve warm with a side of fancy sauce.   coconut oil 2 pounds russet potatoes, sliced salt pepper Makes six servings of fries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granola Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/granola/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/granola/</guid>
      <description>Combine the oats, shredded coconut, nuts, kernels and seeds in a bowl. In a separate bowl combine the honey, sugar, salt, coconut oil and vanilla and mix until sugar is dissolved. Pour liquid over the oats mixture and stir until evenly coated. Spread evenly onto an oiled baking sheet. Bake at 350°F for 20 minutes or until golden brown, turning once.
Remove from the oven and mix in berries. Let cool and break into clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled Skirt Steak Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/grilled_skirt_steak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/grilled_skirt_steak/</guid>
      <description>Mix everything except the steak in a small bowl until the sugar has dissolved. Transfer to a sealable container, add the steak and refrigerate overnight.
Discard marinade and grill steak uncovered, turning at least once, to desired doneness. Remove from the grill and slice into bite-sized strips.
Serve with sides of grilled vegetables and fingerling potatoes.   2 pounds of skirt steak ½ cup soy sauce ½ cup pineapple juice 4 tablespoons brown sugar 2 tablespoons honey 1 green onion, diced 2 garlic cloves, minced Makes two pounds of skirt steak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hombre&#39;s Tacos Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/hombres_tacos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/hombres_tacos/</guid>
      <description>Cut beef into 2″ cubes, lightly salt and pepper and, working in batches to maintain a consistent temperature, brown all sides over medium-high heat in an oiled, preheated skillet. Transfer beef to a slow cooker and combine with salsa. Cover and cook over low heat for four hours. Shred beef using two forks, cover and let stand for 10 minutes.
Remove beef from liquid using slotted spoon or tongs before serving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunter&#39;s Sandwich Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/hunters_sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/hunters_sandwich/</guid>
      <description>On one side of each slice of bread, spread mustard and ranch then sprinkle with salt and pepper. Layer greens, cheese, salami, chips and more greens between the two slices of bread.
Serve immediately with a side of chips.   2 multi-grain bread slices mustard ranch dressing salt black pepper mixed salad greens 1 cheese slice 8 salami slices taro chips Makes one sandwich.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kailua Pork Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/kailua_pork/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/kailua_pork/</guid>
      <description>Preheat oven to 400°F. Cut pork into 2″ cubes. Place half of chopped onion onto the banana leaves and lay pork on top; reserve the remaining onion for serving. Sprinkle pork liberally with salt and liquid smoke. Fold up banana leaves tightly, covering pork completely and securing with twine. Wrap tightly with two layers of aluminum foil.
Place foil package onto a baking pan and bake at an immediately reduced temperature of 300°F up to 6 hours, ensuring meat reaches an internal temperature of at least 145°F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lanikai Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/lanikai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/lanikai/</guid>
      <description>Combine rum with curaçao, pineapple juice, lime juice and coconut syrup. Mix well and pour over ice.
Serve in a tumbler garnished with a lime or pineapple wedge.   1 ounce white rum 1 ounce curaçao 1 ounce pineapple juice 1 lime, juiced 1 tablespoon coconut syrup Makes one drink.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac Salad Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/mac_salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/mac_salad/</guid>
      <description>Whisk milk, mayonnaise, sugar, salt and pepper in a bowl until sugar is dissolved. Set aside.
Cook macaroni until very soft. Drain macaroni and add vinegar while still hot. Toss until absorbed. Let cool for 10 minutes then add dressing, carrots, celery and a salt and pepper to taste. Sprinkle furikake on top and refrigerate for one hour until dressing sets.
Serve chilled.   2 cups milk 2 cups mayonnaise 1 tablespoon brown sugar ½ teaspoon salt 2 teaspoons black pepper 1 pound elbow macaroni ½ cup coconut vinegar 1 carrot, diced 1 celery stalk, diced furikake Makes 10 servings of mac salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marooner&#39;s Jerky Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/marooners_jerky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/marooners_jerky/</guid>
      <description>Place steak into freezer for an hour or until firm but not frozen solid. Remove steak from freezer and slice into thin strips. Combine garlic, onion, pepper, mustard, soy sauce, worcestershire, pineapple juice and rum in a sealable container. Add steak and marinate in refrigerator overnight, rotating at least once.
Remove from refrigerator and let it come to room temperature. Discard marinade and place strips in a single layer onto a large, oiled, oven-safe cooling rack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mokulua Sunrise Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/mokulua_sunrise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/mokulua_sunrise/</guid>
      <description>Fill the glass about two thirds full of equal parts champagne and pineapple juice. Top with chambord.
Serve in a champagne flute.   2 ounces champagne 2 ounces pineapple juice 1 ounce chambord Makes one drink.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New World Pasta Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/new_world_pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/new_world_pasta/</guid>
      <description>Add two tablespoons of oil to a pot large enough to contain everything. Lightly salt and pepper steak and ribs and brown over high heat; set aside. Brown sausage over high heat; drain and set aside.
Cook the garlic, onion, carrot, celery and zucchini until translucent, adding more oil if necessary. Add wine and simmer until almost evaporated. Add ribs, steak, sausage, tomatoes, milk, bay leaves, thyme, basil, salt and a pepper to taste and bring to a simmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omlet Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/omlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/omlet/</guid>
      <description>Whisk milk and eggs together with salt and pepper to preference. Pour milk and egg mixture into lightly oiled, preheated skillet. Cook over medium heat, lifting cooked portion to let uncooked portion flow underneath, until set. Flip, add desired fillings and fold in half, cooking further as desired.
Serve warm with salsa.   1 tablespoon milk 3 eggs salt black pepper anything else Makes one omlet.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Chowder Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pacific_chowder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pacific_chowder/</guid>
      <description>Fry the bacon over high heat. Reduce heat and add the onion, celery and garlic and cook until onions are translucent. Remove mixture from heat and add to slow cooker. Except for heavy cream, add remaining ingredients, including salt and pepper to taste, to slow cooker.
Cook on low for four hours. Remove from heat, discard thyme sprig and bay leaves and stir in heavy cream.
Serve with warm bread and butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacifico Salad Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pacifico_salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pacifico_salad/</guid>
      <description>Create dressing by combining ½ of the cilantro with the garlic, lime juice, honey, cumin and oil. Marinate shrimp overnight in ¼ cup of the dressing and refrigerate the rest.
Discard marinade and saute shrimp in a pre-heated, oiled skillet over medium-high heat for five minutes or until shrimp are pink and cooked through. Set shrimp aside. Add corn to skillet and cook until it begins to char and set aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancakes Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pancakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pancakes/</guid>
      <description>Whisk milk and egg together and set aside. In separate bowl combine flour, baking powder, sugar and salt. Combine the butter, milk and flour mixtures and whisk together. Pour ¼ cup of batter into a lightly oiled, preheated skillet, cooking over medium heat until golden brown on each side.
Serve warm with butter and syrup.   1¼ cups milk 1 egg 1½ cups cake flour 3½ teaspoons baking powder ¼ cup sugar ½ teaspoon salt 3 tablespoons butter, melted Makes 8 pancakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paniolita Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/paniolita/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/paniolita/</guid>
      <description>Combine tequila, triple sec, pineapple juice and lime juice. Mix well and pour over ice.
Serve in li hing mui-rimmed tumbler.   1 ounce tequila blanco 1 ounce triple sec 2 ounces pineapple juice 1 lime, juiced li hing mui powder Makes one drink.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pico de Gallo Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pico_de_gallo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pico_de_gallo/</guid>
      <description>Combine everything including salt and pepper to taste in a bowl and mix well. Refrigerate for 10 minutes to let flavors set.
Serve chilled with tortilla chips.   1 tomato, diced 1 white onion, diced ½ fresh jalapeño, diced ½ lime, juiced ¼ cup cilantro, chopped 1 garlic clove, chopped ¼ teaspoon cumin salt black pepper Makes four servings of salsa.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pineapple Salsa Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pineapple_salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pineapple_salsa/</guid>
      <description>Combine everything including salt to taste in a bowl and mix well. Refrigerate for 10 minutes to let flavors set.
Serve chilled with taro chips.   2 cups pineapple, diced ½ cup cilantro, chopped ¼ cup red onion, chopped 1 serrano pepper, chopped 1 lime, juiced salt Makes four servings of salsa.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plaintains Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/plaintains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/plaintains/</guid>
      <description>Slice plantains cross-wise as thin as you can. Coat with oil and lay in a single layer on aluminum-foil-lined baking sheet. Drizzle with lime juice and sprinkle with salt. Bake at 350°F for 20 minutes, checking constantly and removing individual chips as needed to avoid burning.
Serve immediately or store once cooled.   1 green plantain coconut oil ¼ lime, juiced salt Makes a couple handfuls of chips.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pleasure Point Poke Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pleasure_point_poke/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pleasure_point_poke/</guid>
      <description>Combine mayonnaise, sriracha, vinegar, oil, soy sauce and salt in a large bowl and mix well. Chop ahi into bite sized cubes and add to bowl along with onions, cucumber and avocado. Mix well, cover and refrigerate at least 20 minutes.
Serve chilled on a bed of steamed white rice, sprinkled with furikake and a side of seaweed salad.   ½ cup mayonnaise ¼ cup sriracha 2 teaspoon coconut vinegar 4 teaspoons sesame oil 2 tablespoon soy sauce 2 teaspoon sea salt ½ pound sushi grade ahi tuna ½ cup green onions, diced ½ cup sweet onion, chopped ½ cup chopped cucumber 1 avocado, diced Makes two servings of poke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop-Pop&#39;s Ribs Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pop-pops_ribs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/pop-pops_ribs/</guid>
      <description>Cut rack into individual ribs and place onto foil-covered, oiled baking sheet. Sprinkle with salt and pepper. Bake at 400°F for 15 minutes.
Meanwhile, mix onion, garlic, sugar, vinegar and barbecue sauce in a sauce pan and simmer over medium heat until bubbling. Remove sauce from heat and set aside.
Remove ribs from the oven, coat each rib in sauce and return to the oven. Continue to bake ribs for four hours at a reduced temperature of 300°F, re-coating ribs with sauce every hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potato Salad Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/potato_salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/potato_salad/</guid>
      <description>Boil potatoes in cold, salted water for 20 minutes or until easily pierced with a fork. Drain the potatoes then toss with vinegar. Let the vinegar absorb for 10 minutes. Mix in remaining ingredients including salt and pepper to taste. Refrigerate at least 30 minutes.
Serve chilled.   2 pounds potatoes, diced 2 tablespoons vinegar ½ cup celery, diced ¼ cup sweet onion, diced 1 green onion, diced ¼ cup cilantro, diced 1 garlic clove, minced 2 tablespoons honey 2 teaspoons mustard ½ cup mayonnaise salt black pepper Makes eight servings of potato salad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Brussels Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/roasted_brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/roasted_brussels/</guid>
      <description>Coat the brussels sprouts with oil, salt and pepper to taste. Bake in a single layer on a baking sheet in a preheated oven at 425°F for 20 minutes or until tender and caramelized. Transfer brussels sprouts to a bowl and toss with vinegar and honey.
Serve warm.   1 pound brussels sprouts 2 tablespoons olive oil salt black pepper 1 tablespoon balsamic vinegar 1 teaspoon honey Makes two servings of brussels sprouts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Cream Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/snow_cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/snow_cream/</guid>
      <description>Combine all ingredients with a pinch of salt in a large metal bowl. Place the bowl in the freezer. Remove from the freezer after 10 minutes and scrape the sides with a spatula. Place the bowl back into freezer and repeat until mixture is creamy/crumbly and frozen.
Serve frozen.   2 cups whole milk 2 cups half and half 1 cup sugar 1 tablespoon vanilla extract salt Makes four bowls of ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Bread Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/soda_bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/soda_bread/</guid>
      <description>In a small bowl, mix ¼ cup of the butter with ¼ cup of the buttermilk. Set aside. Combine flour, sugar, baking soda, baking powder, salt and ½ cup of the butter in a large mixing bowl. Add the egg and one cup of the buttermilk and mix well. Remove dough from bowl and gently knead on a lightly floured surface. Form dough into a ball and place onto a buttered baking sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summerdrop Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/summerdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/summerdrop/</guid>
      <description>Muddle the strawberries with the lemon juice and sugar. Add to a shaker with vodka, sour mix and ice. Shake and strain.
Serve in a martini glass.   2 strawberries ½ lemon, juiced 2 teaspoons sugar 2 ounces vodka 2 ounces sour mix Makes one drink.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunbutter Cookies Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/sunbutter_cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/sunbutter_cookies/</guid>
      <description>Preheat oven to degrees. Combine the oil, butter, honey and sugar, egg and vanilla in a large mixing bowl. Mix in the flour, baking powder, baking soda and sunflower kernels to form dough. Place tablespoon-sized portions onto an oiled cookie sheet and bake at 375°F for 10 minutes or until golden brown.
Serve warm or let cool and store.   ½ cup coconut oil ½ cup sunflower seed butter ½ cup honey ½ cup brown sugar 1 egg ½ teaspoon vanilla 1¼ cup flour ½ teaspoon baking powder ½ teaspoon baking soda ½ cup sunflower kernels, roasted Makes 12 cookies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teriyaki-ish Salmon Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/teriyaki-ish_salmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/teriyaki-ish_salmon/</guid>
      <description>Mix everything except the salmon in a small bowl until the sugar has dissolved. Transfer to a sealable container, add the salmon and refrigerate for at least 30 minutes.
Remove the salmon from the marinade and place into an oiled baking dish, skin side down. Drizzle with marinade and bake at 400°F for 15 minutes or until salmon is cooked through and marinade caramelized.
Serve with freshly chopped green onion and a side of steamed white rice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuna Melt Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/tuna_melt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/tuna_melt/</guid>
      <description>Combine tuna, mayonnaise and salt and pepper to taste and set aside. Spread butter on one side of each slice of bread. Spread tuna mixture over one slice of bread, butter-side down. Add cheese and tomato slices and add other slice of bread, butter-side up.
Cook over medium-low heat in a covered, pre-heated skillet, turning at least once, until bread is toasted golden brown and cheese is melted.
Serve warm with a cup of tomato soup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uisce Anann Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/uisce_anann/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/uisce_anann/</guid>
      <description>Combine equal parts whiskey, sour mix and pineapple juice with a splash of soda to preference. Pour over ice.
Serve in a tumbler.   1 ounce irish whiskey 1 ounce sour mix 1 ounce pineapple juice soda Makes one drink.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wushu Salad Recipe from Food Vibes</title>
      <link>http://foodvib.es/recipes/wushu_salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 12:00:00 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://foodvib.es/recipes/wushu_salad/</guid>
      <description>Mix vinegar, oils, sugar, bouillon and salt and pepper to taste in a small bowl. In a large bowl, combine ramen, cabbage, onions and chicken. Add liquid mixture to large bowl and mix well. Refrigerate for at least 30 minutes.
Serve chilled sprinkled with furikake.   3 tablespoons rice vinegar ½ cup roasted sesame oil ½ cup peanut oil 1 teaspoon sugar 1 teaspoon chicken bouillon salt black pepper 1 package dry ramen, crumbled 1 green cabbage, chopped 2 green onions, diced 2 cups cooked chicken, chopped Makes eight bowls of salad.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>